Menu

24-Hour HelpLine: [425-746-1940](tel:425-746-1940) [800-827-8840](tel:1-800-827-8840)

Search for:  

[Home](https://www.lifewire.org/) > [About LifeWire](https://www.lifewire.org/about/) > Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

We are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy discloses how LifeWire collects, protects, and uses the information you provide us online. By using the pages on this site, you are accepting the practices described in the Privacy Policy. If our policy practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting the policy changes here.

Data collection
---------------

LifeWire makes its best effort to respect and protect the privacy of its online visitors. We do not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we do not require you to register or provide information to us to view our site. LifeWire only gathers personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, zip/postal codes, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by a visitor.  
  
For example, we may collect personally identifiable information as part of online donations, event registrations, or email signups. LifeWire staff members only use this information for internal purposes. We do not sell the information you provide to us online to third parties. We will only share personally identifiable information with third parties when (i) the person submitting the information authorizes us to share; (ii) sharing the information is a necessary operation of the site, for instance, to process a credit card transaction; or (iii) as required to by law.

### Collecting personal information through our online donation service

eTapestry processes donations made to LifeWire using our online donation form. You can view eTapestry’s privacy policy on its website.

eTapestry collects a variety of personal information about you to properly process your donation. This personal information may include name, address, phone, email address, credit card information, “acknowledgment” or “in memory of” information, and donation amount. eTapestry maintains this information for LifeWire in their databases. It is unlikely that LifeWire will need to contact you, but we reserve the right if we need to verify your personal information.

### Use of cookies

Visitors should be aware that LifeWire’s website may automatically collect non-personal information and data through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small text files websites use to recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor’s ongoing access to and use of the site, and to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data for content improvements. Cookies are not programs that come onto a visitor’s system and damage files.  
  
If a visitor does not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers allow the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature. LifeWire uses “cookie” technology only to obtain non-personal information from its online visitors to improve visitors’ online experiences and facilitate their visits within our site.

Links to other websites and services
------------------------------------

This site links to other sites and services that LifeWire does maintain. These websites have their own privacy policies, which we encourage you to review. We have no responsibility for linked websites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.

Protecting personal information
-------------------------------

LifeWire takes every precaution to protect donor information. When donors submit sensitive information via our website, we protect their information both online and off-line. When a form asks donors to enter confidential information (such as credit card numbers or addresses), that information is encrypted and protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect donor information off-line. All donor information, not just the confidential information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (our Resource Development Team) have access to personally identifiable information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.

Contacting LifeWire
-------------------

LifeWire works hard to ensure that your giving experience is a positive one. If you would like to have your information removed from our mailing or email lists or if have any questions about this privacy statement, LifeWire’s practices, or this website, please contact us at 425-562-8840 ext. 249 or [comms@lifewire.org](mailto:comms@lifewire.org).

Holiday Shop
------------

[

](https://www.lifewire.org/events/holiday-shop/)

LifeWire’s 2023 Impact Report
-----------------------------

[

](https://www.lifewire.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/2023-Impact-Report.pdf)

Get Social
----------

### FOLLOW LIFEWIRE:

Join Our Email List
-------------------

Email Address \*

First Name 

Last Name 

Select list(s) to subscribe toLifeWire Email List

 Example: Yes, I would like to receive emails from LifeWire. (You can unsubscribe anytime)

Constant Contact Use. Please leave this field blank.

* * *

By submitting this form, you are consenting to receive marketing emails from: . You can revoke your consent to receive emails at any time by using the SafeUnsubscribe® link, found at the bottom of every email. [Emails are serviced by Constant Contact](https://www.constantcontact.com/legal/service-provider)

About
-----

P.O. Box 6398  
Bellevue, WA 98008-0398

Get Help
--------

Get Informed
------------

[

](http://eastsidepathways.org/)

------------------------------------------------------

------------------------------------------

Supported by United Way of King County.

[

](https://www.uwkc.org/)

24 Hour HelpLine
----------------

Copyright © 2022 LifeWire. All rights reserved.  
LifeWire is a 501(c)3 organization.  
Donations are tax-deductible as allowed by law.  

[

](https://www.guidestar.org/profile/91-1190193)
